acuityorg.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy and Policy - Acuityorg.com

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**  
We do not collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Third parties**  
We use third-party companies to display ads on our pages and to track visitor statistics. These companies use information about your visits in order to provide advertisements for this site. Information that is NOT USED: personal information like your name, address, email or phone number; Information that is USED includes: your IP address, country based on your IP address, browser used, the page you are currently visiting, page you came from. Third parties use cookies to display ads based on your prior visits to our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to display ads based on your prior visits to this website and other websites. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by [visiting the advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

Third parties and their privacy policies:  
Google.com - advertising, visitor statistics, +1 Button; [privacy policy of Google.com](http://www.google.com/privacy.html), [Google +1 Button Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/plusone/)  
Facebook.com - fan page, FaceBook like, share and send buttons; [Facebook's Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php)  
Twitter.com - Twitter tweet button; [Twitter Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)   
Pinterest .com - Pinterest pin button; [Pinterest Privacy Policy](http://pinterest.com/about/privacy/)

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml](http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml%20)

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail:jatmiko.personal@gmail.com

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
